Let me explain something. I think when folks come with this narrative of they want to keep us divided, when folks call out black ops, you're missing the point.
Black ops are what divide us. That's their goal.
So the work of pointing them out is to say, we see you and we're not going to listen to you because you are working as an operative.
That's the point. You know, like the division is not about arguing with each other because that's not what those of us are doing.
What we're trying to do is just let you know, hey, that one over there, that one over there, that's not your people.
That's not your people. That's that's what the point is.
And I think some of you think that there's some like intercommunal bickering going on when there are folks who are acknowledging the very loud, problematic,
completely undermining of liberation points of a Kamala Harris, of a Hakeem Jeffries, of a Barack Obama.
I can go on. And you think, oh, by calling these people out, by calling the ways in which they are upholding the system out,
by calling the ways in which they are establishment out, you are being divisive.
No, honey. They are divisive. They are the divide.
What we're trying to do when we call them out is to let them know they have been seen and to give you the chance to see them, too.